kengsub.com 2013-08-06

# KEngSub.com

X

## Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact@kengsub.com. 

At www.kengsub.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.kengsub.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.kengsub.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.kengsub.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.kengsub.com. .:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.kengsub.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: Google Adsense, DramaFever, MGID... 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.kengsub.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.kengsub.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.kengsub.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

X

## Terms of Use 

Your use of this site signifies that you understand and agree to the Terms of Use governing this site. The Terms of Use may be modified at any time and without notice. We encourage you to check back every so often to ensure you are up to date with the Terms of Use. 

**Submitted Content**   
When posting a comment at KEngSub the user agrees not to post any offensive material in any way. KEngSub is an English speaking website, thus when posting a comment, please post in English only. KEngSub reserves the right to edit or remove any material without further notice that is judged to be offensive or inappropriate. 

**Minimum Age**   
You must be at least 13 years of age to use this website. If you are not at least 13 years of age, please do not use this website. 

**Governing Law**   
The governing law will be that of Netherlands, the country in which this site is based and from which all services are provided. 

**Privacy, Spam & Unsolicited Contact**   
This site will unequivocally comply with the requirements of any law enforcement or other officials, Courts, Police or others with a legitimate interest in the official investigation or enforcement of law applicable to the country in which our service is provided, Netherlands.   
The protection of the rights of others is of paramount importance to KEngSub, and this extends to your adherence to intellectual property law, the laws prevailing in your country or residence (or any temporary residence), the rights of others to enjoy freedom from slander, libel, defamation, provocation, harassment, discrimination of any kind or any other action that may be deemed offensive by the individual concerned or the management of this site.   
Users will not be sent unsolicited emails from other parties, although those using "disposable email addresses" (such as "trashmail.net") are warned that such use is forbidden and could result in curtailment of access at any stage.   
Users may not use this site or any facilities provided by this site to spam, market or promote any goods, services, membership or other sites. 

**Disclaimer**  
Videos found on this website are not hosted or uploaded by KEngSub nor is KEngSub affiliated with the video content in any way. All video content is hosted by third party media websites such as youtube.com, veoh.com, dailymotion.com and more. In the case of possible copyright infringement please contact the responsible parties. 

KEngSub operates as an index and database of drama content found publicly available on the Internet. Users who upload to these websites agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts. KEngSub does not take responsibility for the content hosted on such third party websites.
